Dialogs - Info1 
	/Game/Data/dialogs/Dialogs_Level_01.Dialogs_Level_01 - "Trooper Ability: Rapid fire. Increase the fire rate by 2 seconds. One application." 
	/Game/Data/dialogs/Dialogs_Lvl2.Dialogs_Lvl2 - "A Tank is a tenacious fighter who can cover for others. His skill is “Raise shields” protects against shots from a certain direction for 5 seconds! But the tank\'s gun is weak." 

Dialogs - Info2 
	/Game/Data/dialogs/Dialogs_Level_01.Dialogs_Level_01 - "Rifleman Ability: Special ammo. Increase the range and power of the next 4 shots. 2 applications." 
	/Game/Data/dialogs/Dialogs_Lvl2.Dialogs_Lvl2 - "Scout is great for capturing enemy trenches. His shotgun and grenades are powerful, but only suitable for short ranges. Try to combine different units for maximum efficiency!" 

Dialogs - Info3 
	/Game/Data/dialogs/Dialogs_Level_01.Dialogs_Level_01 - "Checkpoints provide resources that can then be spent on buying units. If the resources run out, then defeat will come." 
	/Game/Data/dialogs/Dialogs_Lvl2.Dialogs_Lvl2 - "On the left, you can see how many soldiers have been brought into the battle. The yellow helmet is you. The white one is your living clones. The blue one is a rescued clone. On the right, it shows how far the fighter has progressed on the task." 

